# JANA HATASOVA

Old Trafford, Manchester, UK

Portfolio Website: <a href="https://www.janahatasova.com/">https://www.janahatasova.com/</a>

Email: <a href="mailto:hatasova.j@gmail.com">hatasova.j@gmail.com</a>
Phone number: 07482 990 191

# **ABOUT ME**

I am a self-taught Front End Web Developer. I am on a new career path and developed a great passion for design and building things from scratch. From my previous work experience I learnt how to work under pressure and I always worked within a team. I am a team player and I believe a friendly smiley person. My interests are music, movies, nature.

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### Sep 2019 - Oct 2020 / Caesars Casino, Great Northern, Manchester

- Waitress / Bartender
- Making sure every customer is a happy customer
- Working within a team and very often under pressure
- Being fast and organized was essential

### May 2016 – Sep 2019 / Subway, Piccadilly Station, Manchester

- Team leader
- Making sure there is a good working atmosphere on a shift and the team works well together
- Making sure every customer leaves happy
- Banking, daily paperwork
- Working in a busy environment and under pressure

## **EDUCATION**

2020 – now	Codecademy, Udacity and Udemy courses
2008 - 2009	Business College, Czech Republic
2004 – 2008	Business High School, Czech Republic

## SKILLS

HTML, CSS, SCSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript (ES6), React, Git + Github Responsive Design, Graphic Design, Web Design